camboyslive.com 2001-12-14

# CamBoysLive

Welcome Guest. Please **Create an Account** or **Log-In**  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  

CamBoysLive is committed to maintaining a privacy policy that benefits each individual customer's preferences.

 ** NOTE: Our privacy policy is null and void in cases of fraud!**

This policy explains the privacy practices for Streamray, Inc., a Nevada corporation, located in the state of Nevada (www.Streamray.com). In order to provide interactive computer billing and fraud services, Streamray collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with Streamray in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use. 

  1. **Information Collection:**  
Visitors can access our Web site home page and browse our Web site without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, Streamray may request that you voluntarily supply Streamray with primary personal data (such as name and email address) and identifiers (such as credit card number and web site password). Streamray gives you the option of using a secure transmission method of sending such information.

Streamray receives and stores all information that you enter in our Web site and billing pages. In addition, Streamray collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address, and Streamray employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. However, we do not collect information from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. You are required to provide Streamray with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide Streamray with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with Streamray.

You can inquire about your personal data by sending an e-mail to [customerservice@Streamray.com](mailto:customerservice@Streamray.com). Within a week, Streamray shall provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which Streamray keeps about you. Streamray charges a $25 processing fee for the request. Prior to completing your request, Streamray may require that you provide Streamray with proof of your identity. Streamray reserves the right to refuse any request for information, though Streamray will communicate the reason for its decision. 

  2. **Information Use:**  
Streamray is the sole owner of the information collected on its sites. Streamray will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed it this policy. Streamray shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement, or the contract rights of its clients. Streamray shares the following data with the owner/operator of the web site from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing Streamray services: the URL you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your name, your address, your phone number, your date of birth, and your agreement to be bound by Streamray terms and conditions. Streamray uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Web site, research and development, and fraud deterrence. 
  3. **Information sharing:**  
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 
  4. **Email correspondence:**  
Streamray may request a confirmation when you receive and open and e-mail communication delivered by Streamray. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network. 
  5. **Third party information:**  
Occasionally, Streamray receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to Streamray for fraud prevention purposes. 
  6. **Cookies:**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Streamray employs "cookie" technology. We use Cookie to store personal date, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purpose, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate. 
  7. **Children:**  
Streamray does not request, or knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 18. Streamray takes specific steps to protect the privacy of children by making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our Web site, Streamray requires age verification on every inquiry. Furthermore, Streamray does not give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our web site. 
  8. **Security:**  
We date every protection to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification; unlawful destruction or accidental loss. Streamray utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. Streamray encrypts the information that you provided.

In addition, Streamray does everything to protect your information off-line. All employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. Streamray conducts background and credit checks on all of its employees prior to employment. Streamray employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties. 

  9. **Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to: Administrator, Consumer Protection Dept., Streamray.com Inc., 3764 East Flamingo Road, Las Vegas, NV 89121 or E- mail: [customerservice@Streamray.com](mailto:customerservice@Streamray.com). 

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: Administrator, Consumer Protection Dept., Streamray.com Inc., 3764 East Flamingo Road, Las Vegas, NV 89121 or E- mail: [customerservice@Streamray.com](mailto:customerservice@Streamray.com).  **Important Notice:** All persons whose images are displayed on CamBoysLive are autonomous, work from remote private premises, are neither employees, nor independent contractors of CamBoysLive. CamBoysLive exercises no control over the images displayed by them.  
---  
CamBoysLive.com is best viewed in 800x600 resolution with Netscape 4.0+ or Internet Explorer 4.0+  
Copyright 1999-2001 CamBoysLive.com. _All Rights Reserved_ Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
